codeigniter.com 2014-06-27

# Privacy Policy / About / EllisLab

**Please note that this privacy policy applies to all of EllisLab and our products.**

## Introduction

At EllisLab, Inc. and our affiliated companies we are committed to respecting and protecting your online privacy. We have established this Online Privacy Policy in order for you to understand our policies with regard to your personal information.

## Gathering and Use of Information

EllisLab, Inc. will only collect your personal information when you purchase our products, or when you voluntarily sign-up for a membership account in order to access certain areas of our site, or when you sign-up for our mailing list. Access to our web site is generally unrestricted, and you may browse it anonymously.

Information we collect from you will never be sold, rented, or shared with third-parties. However, we may need to share your information with our affiliated companies in order to provide services you have purchased or requested. We will make you aware of such instances.

## Cookies

Our website utilizes “cookies”. A “cookie” is a small text file that permits us to recognize your browser in order to customize your experience, or permit you to access restricted areas. Cookies do not contain personal information.

## IP Address

Your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address is usually associated with the place from which you enter the Internet, like your Internet Service Provider, your company or your university. We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, gather broad demographic information, and administer our Web site.

## Mailing Lists

As a member of our Web site you may occasionally receive an email newsletter informing you of new products and services. You may choose not to receive further email messages by clicking the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of the email.

## Commitment

We are committed to privacy and support industry initiatives to preserve individual privacy rights on the Internet. Questions regarding this policy may be sent to: [corporate@ellislab.com](mailto:corporate@ellislab.com).

## Contact Us

Please review our [Support F.A.Q.](https://support.ellislab.com/faq "Our Sales F.A.Q.") or email us at [sales@ellislab.com](mailto:sales@ellislab.com)

### General correspondence
